Qin Molin,
تشين مولين ،
why don't you wake up?
لماذا لا تستيقظ
If anything happens to you,
إذا حدث لك أي شيء ،
I'll feel guilty for the rest of my life.
سأشعر بالذنب لبقية حياتي.
Ever since I came here,
منذ أن جئت إلى هنا ،
you've been saving me.
كنت تنقذني.
Although at the beginning,
رغم أنه في البداية ،
you must have other intentions.
يجب أن يكون لديك نوايا أخرى.
However,
لكن،
in the later days,
في الأيام اللاحقة ،
I saw your true heart.
رأيت قلبك الحقيقي.
Can you help me find Juan?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في العثور على خوان؟
Catch Chen Jie,
قبض على تشين جي ،
you've been protecting me subconsciously,
كنت تحميني دون وعي ،
He even did a lot of things
حتى أنه فعل الكثير من الأشياء
for me behind my back.
بالنسبة لي خلف ظهري.
Qin Molin,
تشين مولين ،
wake up, okay?
استيقظ ، اتفقنا؟
I really can't live without you.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع العيش بدونك.
Stop crying.
توقف عن البكاء.
I will feel distressed.
سوف أشعر بالحزن.
Are you pretending to be dizzy?
هل تتظاهر بالدوار؟
I just want to know
انا فقط اريد ان اعرف
what's on your mind.
في ماذا تفكر.
Qin Molin,
تشين مولين ،
go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
You scared me.
لقد أخفتني.
It seems that I don't have a chance at all.
يبدو أنه ليس لدي فرصة على الإطلاق.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
How's your strength?
كيف هي قوتك؟
Not bad, right?
ليس سيئا ، أليس كذلك؟
I did so well,
لقد قمت بعمل جيد جدا ،
can you stop being angry with me?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن الغضب مني؟
I'll think about it.
سأفكر بشأنه.
Su,
نكون،
Su
هم انهم
What the heck?
ي للرعونة؟
Su,
نكون،
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Would you like to go back to the palace with me
هل تود العودة معي إلى القصر
and be my empress?
وتكون إمبراطوريتي؟
This is too straight.
هذا مستقيم جدا.
Don't look at me like that.
لا تنظر إلي هكذا.
I can't take it anymore.
أنا غير قادر على اتخاذ ذلك بعد الآن.
Su
هم انهم
Su Jinxia, what are you doing?
سو جينشيا ، ماذا تفعل؟
As a woman of the new era,
كامرأة في العصر الجديد ،
it's unreasonable for you to be so coy.
من غير المعقول أن تكون خجولًا جدًا.
Gosh,
يا الهي ،
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
Actually, I like you too.
في الواقع ، أنا معجب بك أيضًا.
But I don't want to go back to the palace with you to be the empress.
لكني لا أريد أن أعود إلى القصر معك لأكون الإمبراطورة.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Are you afraid that
هل انت خائف من ذلك
after you return to the palace,
بعد عودتك للقصر
There will be no freedom.
لن تكون هناك حرية.
The empress is really not a human being,
الإمبراطورة ليست إنسانًا حقًا ،
not only do you not have enough to eat,
ليس فقط ليس لديك ما يكفي من الطعام ،
And there are many rules,
وهناك العديد من القواعد ،
not to mention,
ناهيك عن،
Your Majesty, your harem is so beautiful,
جلالة الملك ، حريمك جميل جدا ،
I don't want to share a husband with others.
لا أريد مشاركة زوج مع الآخرين.
Three thousand weak water,
ثلاثة آلاف ماء ضعيف ،
I'll only take one ladle.
سآخذ مغرفة واحدة فقط.
It's not a problem.
ليست مشكلة.
I promise you.
أعدك.
After I return to the palace,
بعد أن أعود إلى القصر ،
I will issue an imperial edict,
سأصدر مرسومًا إمبراطوريًا ،
You're the only one in the harem.
أنت الوحيد في الحريم.
If you never accept a consort,
إذا لم تقبل مطلقًا زوجة ،
I won't restrict your freedom.
لن أقيد حريتك.
I won't let you be burdened by the imperial rules.
لن أتركك تثقل كاهل القواعد الإمبراطورية.
Besides,
بجانب،
didn't you say,
ألم تقل
The original intention of opening a large-size women's clothing store,
النية الأصلية لفتح متجر ملابس نسائي كبير الحجم ،
is to help people like Juan.
هو مساعدة الناس مثل خوان.
If you become the empress,
إذا أصبحت الإمبراطورة ،
you can do more than that.
يمكنك أن تفعل أكثر من ذلك.
Su,
نكون،
are you willing to
هل انت راغب ان
change this country with me?
غير هذه الدولة معي؟
Verbal statements
البيانات الشفهية
have no evidence. We have to prove it with written evidence.
ليس لديهم دليل.  علينا إثبات ذلك بالأدلة المكتوبة.
First,
أولاً،
you must always like Su Jinxia alone,
يجب أن تحب Su Jinxia دائمًا ،
Don't change your mind,
لا تغير رأيك ،
or the scissors will serve you.
أو المقص سوف يخدمك.
Second,
ثانيا،
let Su Jinxia eat well,
دع Su Jinxia يأكل جيدًا ،
Drink well
اشرب جيدا
and you'll be free.
وستكون حرا.
Third,
ثالث،
quarrel with Su Jinxia,
مشاجرة مع Su Jinxia ،
You must admit your mistake.
يجب أن تعترف بخطئك.
What if you're wrong?
ماذا لو كنت مخطئا؟
Su Jinxia is always right.
Su Jinxia دائما على حق.
Add this too.
أضف هذا أيضًا.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
For the late wedding night,
في وقت متأخر من ليلة الزفاف ،
you have to make it up to me.
عليك أن تعوضها لي.
When you put on my princess dress,
عندما ترتدي فستان أميرتي ،
you will be very beautiful,
ستكونين جميلة جدا
which means beautiful.
مما يعني الجمال.
Director Zhu,
مدير تشو ،
Hey,
يا،
There's a new style.
هناك أسلوب جديد.
The new goods from the group headquarters have arrived.
وصلت البضائع الجديدة من مقر المجموعة.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Armistice agreement?
اتفاقية الهدنة؟